<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cms on Tachon</title><link>https://fasterthanlight.net/cms/</link><description>Recent content in Cms on Tachon</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://fasterthanlight.net/cms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Adding Tachyon to Google Tag Manager</title><link>https://fasterthanlight.net/cms/google-tag-manager/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fasterthanlight.net/cms/google-tag-manager/</guid><description>← Home
Click me to copy!
Google Tag Manager is one of the best ways to add Tachyon to your website. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to use and allows you to add Tachyon to any website, even if you don&amp;rsquo;t have access to the code.
Copy the &amp;lt;script&amp;gt; tags above Go to Google Tag Manager Click “Tags” and then “New” Click “Tag Configuration” and select “Custom HTML” Paste the &amp;lt;script&amp;gt; tags you copied into the Tag Configuration “HTML” field Click on the &amp;ldquo;Triggering&amp;rdquo; section below &amp;ldquo;Tag Configuration&amp;rdquo; Select the &amp;ldquo;All Pages&amp;rdquo; option from the &amp;ldquo;Choose a trigger&amp;rdquo; menu Click save, and set the tag name to &amp;ldquo;Tachyon&amp;rdquo; Enjoy your faster website!</description></item><item><title>Adding Tachyon to Shopify</title><link>https://fasterthanlight.net/cms/shopify/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fasterthanlight.net/cms/shopify/</guid><description>← Home
Click me to copy!
Shopify makes it easy to add Tachyon.
Copy the &amp;lt;script&amp;gt; tags above Login to your Shopify store Navigate to the &amp;ldquo;Online Store&amp;rdquo; section Click on Themes and then on the “Customize” button. Click on the 3 dots next to the name of the theme in the top left corner In the dropdown menu, click “Edit code” Click on the theme.liquid file in the file navigator on the left Look for a line that reads &amp;lt;head&amp;gt; at the top of the file Paste the &amp;lt;script&amp;gt; tags you copied on the line just below the line that reads &amp;lt;head&amp;gt; Click &amp;ldquo;Save&amp;rdquo; in the top right corner Enjoy your faster storefront!</description></item><item><title>Adding Tachyon to Squarespace</title><link>https://fasterthanlight.net/cms/squarespace/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fasterthanlight.net/cms/squarespace/</guid><description>
← Home
Click me to copy!
Squarespace makes it very easy to add Tachyon.
Copy the &amp;lt;script&amp;gt; tags above In the Squarespace home menu, click on &amp;ldquo;Settings&amp;rdquo; Click on &amp;ldquo;Advanced&amp;rdquo; Click on &amp;ldquo;Code Injection&amp;rdquo; Paste the &amp;lt;script&amp;gt; tags you copied into the &amp;ldquo;Header&amp;rdquo; field Click save Voila! Enjoy your faster website!</description></item><item><title>Adding Tachyon to Webflow</title><link>https://fasterthanlight.net/cms/webflow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fasterthanlight.net/cms/webflow/</guid><description>← Home
Click me to copy!
Webflow makes it very easy to add Tachyon.
Copy the &amp;lt;script&amp;gt; tags above Login to your Webflow designer Select Project settings from the top left nav menu Select &amp;ldquo;Custom Code&amp;rdquo; from the horizontal nav bar Paste the &amp;lt;script&amp;gt; tags you copied into the Head Code textbox Click save changes Publish the changes to your site Et voila! Your Webflow site will have never felt so fast!</description></item><item><title>Adding Tachyon to Wix</title><link>https://fasterthanlight.net/cms/wix/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fasterthanlight.net/cms/wix/</guid><description>← Home
Click me to copy!
Wix makes it very easy to add Tachyon.
Copy the &amp;lt;script&amp;gt; tags above Login to your Wix dashboard Hover over the site where you want to add Tachyon and click on “Select &amp;amp; Edit site&amp;quot; Click on “Settings” on the left menu Click on “Advanced” and then &amp;ldquo;Custom code&amp;rdquo; Click on “Add Custom code” Paste the &amp;lt;script&amp;gt; tags you copied earlier into the “Paste the code snippet here” field Set the &amp;ldquo;Name&amp;rdquo; field to &amp;ldquo;Tachyon&amp;rdquo; In the “Add Code to Pages,” select “All Pages” Set the &amp;ldquo;Place code in&amp;rdquo; field to &amp;ldquo;Head&amp;rdquo; Click on “Code Type” on top of the “Add Custom Code” Window, choose the appropriate type Click on “Apply” Congratulations!</description></item><item><title>Adding Tachyon to WordPress</title><link>https://fasterthanlight.net/cms/wordpress/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fasterthanlight.net/cms/wordpress/</guid><description>← Home
Adding Tachyon to WordPress is easier than ever. Just follow these steps:
Download the Tachyon plugin for WordPress Log into your WordPress admin panel In the menu, click on &amp;ldquo;Plugins&amp;rdquo; then &amp;ldquo;Add New&amp;rdquo; In the top left corner, click on &amp;ldquo;Upload Plugin&amp;rdquo; Upload the tachyon.zip file you downloaded earlier Tachyon will install and you will be redirected Click on &amp;ldquo;Activate Plugin&amp;rdquo; Voila! Your WordPress site will feel faster than ever!</description></item></channel></rss>